PENG WEI

full stack web developer

626-382-6284|edmondwei1987@gmail.com github: https://github.com/edmondwei1987 linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pengwei87

portfolio: https://edmondwei1987.github.io

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer proficient in MEAN, Python with Django and Ruby on Rails stack with the ability to develop web applications from concept to implementation. I have computer science related bachelor degree and used to work in two companies for 3 years as a software engineer in Beijing, China. Complete 14 weeks programming training in web develop. I am good at solving problems in the projects and would like to cooperate with others. I am seeking a opportunity to make some exciting products to make life easier.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Beijing, China; Founder International Co., software engineer (2012-2014)

develop Clinical Data Repository system worked closely with senior developer and learned how to use programming framework to deal with data design and modify the view pages for the CDR system

Beijing, China; Softtek, software engineer(2011-2012)

maintain and redevelopment for the audi online employee assessment system complete parts of the logical coding and also maintain the database

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, 2018

Coding Dojo, Burbank, CA

12 week full-time web development training program, gaining nearly 1000 hours of intensive coding experience including the introduction, implementation, and iteration of various web projects over 3 full stacks.

Bachelor, Information Management and Information System

Northwest A&F University -- Xi'an, China -- 2006-2010

TECHNICAL SKILLLS

Languages

javascript, ruby, python, java, SQL

Database

MongoDB,SQLite,MySQL

Frameworks

Angular 5, Express, Node.js, ruby on rails

Development Tools

Sublime Text, Visual Studio Editor

ORM

Mongoose, ActiveRecord

Front-End

HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, bootstrap, Ajax

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Fruit Mart

Single person project building a platform for people to trade fruit in their backyards. A user can post his fruit in the website and other buyers can view these fruits on their favor. They can also search based on the zip code.

Technologies

Javascript, JQuery, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, Angular4, Node.js, bootstrap

Weather Forecast

A simple website shows weather information in 6 big cities in U.S.

Technologies

Express.js, Angular4, Node.js, bootstrap, weather API(OpenWeatherMap)